Thank you for watching.
And here we go. Nogizaka Tsuminaka, your host, Bananaman.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much for your hard work. Go out there and win!
Yay!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh! Color-coded!
Yes, yes...
Phew.
Oh, my goodness.
Ready.
Rumble, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, rattle, ping pong
Who's going to sing?
Come on, come on, today's project, Mr. Himura.
Please do it!
Let's sing Nogizaka!
Yes!
We did it!
Yay!
On this night, song-loving members were divided into three teams for a big karaoke competition!
The rules are simple: If you answer the intro quiz correctly, you get the right to sing the song!
The teams sang only the chorus of the song and the score of the song was the team's score.
Which team will sing the song and win the first Nogizaka King of Karaoke?
We've done some research on the past winners of this kind of game, and we're by far the strongest.
We love intro quizzes, so we'll be on the Bananaman team this time, too.
We're the defending champions, so it's all about the score.
That's how the team scores.
If you arrange it, it's no good. If Koji Taruki is on, you can't arrange it.
You have to sing it exactly as it is.
The winning team gets employee muscats from the line-drawer shop.
That's nice. I'm usually happy. Nice, I'm usually happy.
One for each of us!
Mr. Mezawa, now that you've gone upscale, there's only one for each of you.
I'm impressed that you noticed that right away.
You're going to take it home and eat it slowly.
But what do you think?
Who likes karaoke the most?
I go to karaoke all the time.
Of course he does.
But I only sing what I like.
Who's your favorite by the way?
I sing a lot of Vocaloid songs.
Maybe he's not in it.
I heard they have a "Best Hits" list for each decade.
If you go to a karaoke place, you might be able to find a song you like from there.
I hear there's a pretty wide range of ages.
Maybe Okada knows some of the old songs.
Songs your mom or dad used to listen to.
Which ones did your mom and dad listen to?
Green.
That's really old?
That was so fabulous!
You know, you just made a bunch of old guys crack up.
I was like, "What's green?
That's amazing.
Yuta and the others...
They don't know the song, but it's usually sung by someone else.
I see.
Nakanishi is good, isn't he? Nakanishi is good, isn't he?
Is that so?
You already know you're good.
Nakanishi's good.
Thank you.
You don't have to be so modest.
Nogizaka's team will have three members each.
Now it's time for the Uta-Oh!
No moves will be made.
So you can go ahead and do your thing.
Let's get to it!
Nogizaka Uta-Oh!
Thank you for watching!
Wow! He's good!
I don't know.
Okay, yellow team.
You got it?
Oh, no!
Aisa Otsuka's cherries.
Correct!
That's great!
Now then, you have won the right to sing the chorus song!
I heard it's hard to get the notes because it starts from the chorus.
Yeah...
Because it starts from the chorus
Yoda sings for the yellow team!
I wonder how many points I can get at karaoke!
If you don't get the first verse, you're in trouble.
Oh!
He's so cute. Cute.
One more time.
I'm gonna throw in one score with this.
I'm nervous.
Thirty-six, 64, 79.
Oh, shit.
Ninety-one.
Oh, no, I got 90.
On a side note, you don't hit at all!
I was so nervous standing here.
But I've seen it once, so everyone understands.
I get it.
You're in trouble if you don't answer.
I already got a 91.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Okay.
Let's sing!
Not so fast!
Wait a minute.
Heshi, I've heard of you.
It's time...
What was that?
Jupiter.
Oh, man, if I knew better, I wouldn't understand it that fast.
Here you go, Blue Team!
Risa-san's HomuraHomura by Risa
Homura.
That's the second song.
This one's tough.
The corpse of a thief tries to sing the chorus of a popular anime song!
Damn, I wish I could have sung it!
Thank you for watching!
[Applause]
We're going to get the score right.
We're going to get the score right, and now the last one, too.
Mizumi's good.
I don't know how you can go that high all of a sudden.
I was so nervous!
You've sung this before?
Yes, I have.
That's high.
This is high.
92.1 seconds.
Oh, no, no, no!
That team's at the top.
But, Himura, it's good, it's good, it's good.
You have to go that fast to get it.
If you don't go that fast, you won't get the intro.
Oh, no.
The team's in a hurry.
I know it all, and I'm pushing, but...
But if the blue and yellow go for another song, we'll be in a big hurry.
Okay, here we go.
Let's go!
Let's sing Nogizaka!Let's Sing Nogizaka
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Blue team
Red Team
Shirushi ai no shirushi
Correct
This is...
Well, you know, generationally speaking.
We're called the puffins of the comedy world.
They don't say that.
No, they don't.
Yumiki.
Yumiki's good.
Even if you're not very good.
You guys...
You guys
You are
Oh, man.
Good
Oh my God!
What tire tayoumiki score?
Wow!
Oh no!
94.363 points94.363 points.
Oh no, I've got zero points... yet.
I know, but I can't get it.
It's so frustrating.
I mean, it's only one point.
But...
Is this going to happen?
You do this all the time.
I'll do it once.
Thank you.
What's this for?
I don't know.
Complaint.
Maybe you don't know what it is.
Red Team.
We're going to live.
Oh, shit.
Ready?
Turn it on.
Got it.
I got the song right.
I'm so happy.
They got it wrong.
Of course, it's Himura who sings.
Will the big fermentation make a big comeback?
Thank you for your hard work.
Up, up, up, up! Score, score, score!
Go!Go!
Okay, 33.
Bring it, bring it, bring it.
What? What?
You're kidding?
What? What? What?
82.364.
What? ? Huh?
Why aren't you in the 90s?
What? We're the worst!
Poor little guy. Poor little guy.
Poor you! Poor you! Poor you!
What?
So far, each team has answered one question correctly.
Let's see which team can pull it out.
Let's go! The Nogizaka Uta King!
Let's go! Car Team Aiko's Beetles!
I can't remember the last time I saw a beetle start like this.
I'm impressed.
Okuda sings the song after winning the first place!
The end!
Thank you for watching!
[Applause]
You know, in a case like that, it's great that you can go to a show like that.
I'll give you the price, and I'll give you a big win, and I'll give you a 92.
I'm so glad I got this one.
I have a left thigh too........
Mari, let's sing!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do a few songs at the gachan.Some songs in a jumble.
We've got a lot of songs.
Seino
One Night Carnival
Congratulations!
Shirara's first song was
Thank you for watching
Thank you very much for watching.
[Applause]
I'm not sure if the Bananaman team will be able to extend the privilege of being an idiot or not.
Ah!
Yes, yes, yes, go!
Oh, what's this?
What's this?
Wait a minute!
You've got satay in your satchel!
I feel sorry for him.
We're going to go for it!
We're going!
Why are we the only ones singing in Nogizaka's show?
All right, here we go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's sing "Nogizaka"!
Come on, red team, USHIBA!
I know, I know... This is hard.
Lilia Ito tries a difficult song.
Oh, nice!
Oh, nice! Oh, nice.
Oh, nice.
You can't sing this off the top of your head.
You've never sung it before?
Yes, I've never sung it before.
Lilia Ito scored 83 points.
Next, Question 8.
Let's go on and on!
Unao Nozaka
Oh, I'll sing something.
I wonder if it would be good if I could sing
Everything's expensive.
What's that? What's that?
Twice... twice the same song.
No, Ima-san's a beetle.
Beetle!
Hey, your hand's a little high.
Wait a minute. Oh, here it comes! Red!
What? A glorious run?
No, no, no.
Yuh-oh!
Glorious Kake-Ashika!
- Let's go! It's warm. Yuzuike-den.
- What? I don't understand!
- You must be low on points to understand!
- It's a warm Yuzu garden.
- What you don't understand is low!
- What do you mean, "What do you mean, what do you mean, what do you mean?
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thanks for your time.
No, it's a famous song even if you don't know it surprisingly
I knew you could sing it.
Yeah, I did.
Iwamoto, who had no reception
Scored as high as 92 points
Oh, man, it's red.
It's overwhelmingly strong.
Oh no.
One point, though.
So cool!
Then, Mr. Himura...
Look, there it is.
A little high performance.
Hey, you're eating that.
The same one twice.
I'm a real uncle now.
Here we go.
Ready, set, go!
Let's sing "No-gi-saka"!
What's this?
Wow!
Yes! Yellow!
366 days.
Wow!
That's my favorite song.
I love that song.
That's a great song.
That's a great song.This is a super good song.
Yellow team is Nakanishi's first karaoke.
Oh!
This is good.
That's good.
I love this.
Oh, I love this one.
Love sister... ah! Have you ever sung this before?
I've only heard of it, but it tastes like it... The highest bonus score so far was a 95!
Here it is, the highest score of the day, before singing
Thank you so much!
The blue team's trailing by a few points... but will they be able to catch up?
Let's go!
Let's sing!
Let's sing Nogizaka!
It's the red team!
That's right!
That's what I'm talking about!
And here's a slightly anxious-looking Onoki singing karaoke for the first time!
Thank you for watching!
I made a mistake.
I think I made a mistake...
I put in "inoki".
Why did you put in the inoki? Why is the inoki
What was the score of such an inoki?
Why, how many points did you just get?
But it was 80.
How come it's higher than ours?
Why is it higher than ours?
How come it's 87.001?
It's 87.001.
Did you know about the touch? But...
I know the touchy-feely part.
I thought I could do it in a hurry.
You got it.
They're usually higher than us.
That's funny.
It's getting stronger and stronger.
Here we go.
Ready?
We're losing.
Another one.
It's gone.
This is fast.
I have no idea.
Eeepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepepep
Shigawa-san's elongated step
It's so fast!
Also fast.
Red
Gedo chew
Gedotchu.
Gedotchu, no.Geddeschu, no.
Let's hear it one more time.
Everybody hands off!
Everybody hands off.
Let's hear it one more time.
No, no, no, no.
Play the song, listen to it, then press play.
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay, let's hear the song, please.
Yay!
It's going "kacha-kacha-kacha-kacha-kacha"!
It was so loud, I couldn't hear anything.
What?
Isn't that recent?
I don't know.
Mrs. Green Apple.
What?
Will you shut up?
Mrs. Green Apple.
That's it.
No, I don't get it then.
Medium diversity.
Oh, it's strong.
Oh, that one.
Oh, that's her.
Not Mrs. Green Apple at all!
The red team challenged Iwamoto again
Red team challenges Iwamoto again!Red team challenges Iwamoto again
Yes!
Good!
It's good!
You were saying that?
Yes!
OK!
Score is only 86.
Huh.
You can't do that.
All right.
And the red team continues to run solo.
What?
But here's the one that bit the dust...
Yes!
You got it? You got it?
Red suidippi!
Seiko Matsuda's famous song.
What?
I don't feel like it.
What's this?
Himura answered correctly and sang for a high score.
The result was
What's wrong with this?
I'm only getting 4 on 8 with this.
We're both in a red fight, so you'd better push blue and yellow.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Let's sing "Nogizaka.Let's sing Nogizaka!
What's this?
Ao.
Seino
I'll call it a night
Hey!
I wonder if that's a night out now. I've heard so much about night outs.
Here is the youngest Ogawa doing karaoke for the first time today!
Oh, you're so good
You're so good.
Ogawa's solo. I've only been to karaoke with my family alone.
I was so nervous!
Oh, man... the chorus of "Nightlife" is so good.
Out of the blue!
Blue team got 88 points with Ogawa's singing!
Can they catch up to the red team?
We've got to go for it, Blue and Yellow!
Oh, no!
Let's go!
Here we go!
Ready?
Let's sing Nogizaka!
It's totally fine.
Definitely not for girls.
Se-no.
One of 240 million
Two hundred and forty million.
That's great.
Of course, Hiromi sings.Of course it's Hiromi who sings.
Thank you very much.
Here comes the big Hiromi!
It's the chorus.
Good morning.
Good morning
Good MorningGood Morning
Good Morning
Good morning
Oh Kei, it's okay
It's so dangerous.
I'm going.
I went over 90.
Why don't you go?
Why didn't you go over 90?
Why not?
I'm Akira Kobayashi.
Cover Tube
Hi, I'm Lilia Ito.
I'm Haruka Kuromi.
We're going to play rock-paper-scissors-paper by tapping and covering.
Let's start!
Tap, cover, and play rock-paper-scissors-paperKnock, cover, rock, paper, scissors, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
It's a pairing, right?
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
So it was a tie.
A tie.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a rating!
Please subscribe to our channel!